ANAGHA R

anagharaj95@gmail.com

944686933

Calicut

PROFILE

Passionate and hardworking Software Engineer with 2 years of experience in IOT application development in python language and maintenance using open source applications. Worked in research of new IOT technologies for the team in short span of time.

WORK EXPERIENCE

05/2018 - Present Software Engineer | Ripples IOT(Software Associates Information

Technologies) Calicut India

Developed real-time environment and Condition monitoring IoT software using Zigbee technology.

Experience in working with data visualization tools.

Experience in working in Asset Management system with RFID(Radio-frequency identification) and node-red.

Experience in open source application design, development and architecture.

Experience in working on BLE technology

05/2017 - 05/2018 Junior Programmer | Software Associates Information Technologies

calicut

Worked in Data analysis and forecasting using R programming. Basic working experience in Drupal platform

INTERNSHIP | KELTRON KNOWLEDGE CENTER, Calicut

Worked on basic linux administration.

Online Feedback System: Worked on an online feedback system for the students to evaluate their teachers.

EDUCATION

08/2013 - 05/2017 B.Tech (Computer Science & Engineering) - 6.43 CGPA | National Institute of

Technology, Calicut

04/2012 - 05/2013 XII - 89.6% | Govt Senior Secondary School, Kavaratti, Lakshadweep

04/2009 - 05/2010 X - 9.8 CGPA | Kendriya Vidyalaya kavaratti

SKILLS

ІоТ	RPi3, Node Red,Grafana, MQTT, RFID, Zigbee	Expert
Scripting Languages	Python,R	Expert
Databases	InfluxDB,PostgreSQL,MySQL	Expert
Programming Languages	JavaScript	Intermediate
Web Technologies	Drupal, HTML,CSS,Django	Beginner